<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-07-25T11:33:30-05:00</updated><id>https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/feed.xml</id><title type="html">fastpages</title><subtitle>An easy to use blogging platform with support for Jupyter Notebooks.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Cheatsheet for Simple Things in Python</title><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2022/07/25/python_cheat_sheet.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cheatsheet for Simple Things in Python" /><published>2022-07-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-07-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2022/07/25/python_cheat_sheet</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Format numbers with commas in a print statement</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Running the Fastai Course on my Local Machine</title><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/21/fastai-course-on-local-computer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Running the Fastai Course on my Local Machine" /><published>2021-08-21T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-08-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/21/fastai-course-on-local-computer</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was working through the first few chapters of the Fast.ai Fastbook course using the recommended free tier on paperspace. It worked well well except it was usually about 5-10 minutes before a virtual machine was available and I frequently got dropped 30-60 minutes after getting access. It wasn’t a big deal but it usually meant a 10-15 min pause before I could get back to work. The course recommends using preconfigured PAAS solutions instead running locally because of the difficulty setting up your environment, which can be a real pain. Alas, curiosity got the best of me, I really wanted to try to run the fastai package on my local machine.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Adding a Photo to a Fastpages Blog Post</title><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/14/adding-images-to-fastpages-blog-posts.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adding a Photo to a Fastpages Blog Post" /><published>2021-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/14/adding-images-to-fastpages-blog-posts</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I was confused by Fastpages’ instruction on how to add a photo to a post. This is how I do it when writing a post in markdown:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Switching from Online Class to Hybrid Model</title><link href="https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/13/return-to-inperson-school.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Switching from Online Class to Hybrid Model" /><published>2021-08-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-08-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://robbdunlap.github.io/robbo_and_the_realers/2021/08/13/return-to-inperson-school</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’m about a third of the way through my MS in Data Analytics. I decided to get my degree through a traditional graduate school program because I wanted to interact with the professors directly and get to know my fellow students. Then, COVID came along just before I started school and all of my classes switched to online. There are some drawbacks to learning online, such as it takes a while to get questions answered instead of just being able to ask the professor directly during class, as well as having very limited relationships with any of my fellow students. School is a good opportunity to increase the number of people you know in your field and thus increase your chance of finding a good job. Also, it’s great to be able to work through tough concepts with fellow students when you inevitably hit a roadblock.</summary></entry></feed>